# Anjali Upadhyay

### UI developer







https://www.linkedin.com/in/ anjali-upadhyay-b261347b/

#### Career Objective

A dynamic professional with nearly 5+ years of extensive experience in HTML development, web development and designing. Consists of a good team work and team spirit as well as when I opt to work individually I can prefer the same caliber.

#### **Education**

MCA-2014-16

LNCT Bhopal- 8.06 CGPA

BCA-2011-2014

MCNUJC Bhopal- 77%

#### **Work Experience**

April 2021 – Present Profile

TCS UI Developer

Nov 2019 – May 2021 Profile

Growel Softech Pvt. UI Developer

Ltd

May 2019 – Oct 2019 Profile

Corvi LED pvt ltd, Sr. UI Developer

Mumbai

Sept 2017- April 2019 Profile

Pexitics, Bangalore Software Developer

#### Links of my work

- Corvi
- Pexitics
- Pexiscore
- PexiticsBlog
- Careergraph
- Benchmarkevents

#### **Professional Skills**

- HTML
- CSS
- Wordpress
- Bootstrap
- Javascript
- JQuery
- Edison lite
- Hugo
- Canvas
- Photoshop
- Bitbucket
- Git
- Azure
- Prezi

#### Personal Skills

0

Teamwork



Flexibility



Leadership



Hard Work



Communication



Managing

#### **Hobbies**









#### **Projects**

## Website development

Role-Development Designing of the sites multiple pages. Making forms for registration and login. Discussion with the team about the inabilities and functionalities as per requirement. Tools used – Hugo, EdisonLite, Html, CSS, JQuery, canvas.

#### E-Commerce Website

Role-Designing Designing of the sites multiple pages. Making forms for buying. Discussion with the team about the inabilities and functionalities as per requirement. Tools used - .Net, Pl/sql, Html, Css, Bootstrap, Js, Jquery.

#### HR Assessment

Role- Web development

UI designing of the whole website including form, assessment, resume and report part of the candidate. Dashboard and candidate shortlisting and job interview scheduling for the HR.. Tools used - .Net, Pl/sql, Html, Css, Bootstrap, Js, Jquery, Ajax, Angular 2.

### Company's website

Role- Web development Designing and development of whole website. Technology used: .Net Core 2, MVC, JS, JQuery, Ajax, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap. Main role was to design the template and convert the same to HTML.

#### Blog site

Role- Web development

Creating blog site using wordpress, used wordpress plugin and customized CSS for the pages, managing roles of author and subscribers. Tools used - Wordpress Html, Css, Bootstrap, Wordpress plugins.